<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Faqs on Schulich Ignite</title><link>https://schulichignite.com/faq/</link><description>Recent content in Faqs on Schulich Ignite</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://schulichignite.com/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://schulichignite.com/faq/cost/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://schulichignite.com/faq/cost/</guid><description>Our sessions are completely free for all. All that we ask is that you bring your enthusiasm and passion for programming!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://schulichignite.com/faq/friends_faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://schulichignite.com/faq/friends_faq/</guid><description>Yes! If you would like to be grouped with your friends who are also joining the program, simply list their names in the sign up survey, and we will do the rest!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://schulichignite.com/faq/gain_out_of_it_faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://schulichignite.com/faq/gain_out_of_it_faq/</guid><description>Through the Schulich Ignite program, you will be able to develop as aprogrammer all the way from gaining basic coding skills all the way to becoming a proficient and certified software developer.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://schulichignite.com/faq/help/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://schulichignite.com/faq/help/</guid><description>We are always recruiting for mentors, content-developers, and commisoners!
Join our mailing list for details about when we begin recruitment</description></item><item><title/><link>https://schulichignite.com/faq/online_or_in_person/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://schulichignite.com/faq/online_or_in_person/</guid><description>We will have two formats for our sessions this semester:
Hybrid: We will have the ENG G 203 room booked in the Schulich School of Engineering Building,on the University of Calgary Campus, for students that have access to this form of transport.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://schulichignite.com/faq/suitable_faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://schulichignite.com/faq/suitable_faq/</guid><description>Our programs are aimed at ages between 11-21 (this is not enforced though), our 3 courses range from an gentle introduction to programming in python, to advanced programming methodologies with the aid of Object-Oriented programming, and lastly our Web-development course which builds on the advanced programming methodologies in the field of Websites and many more cool technologies which will help you build and maintain your website!</description></item></channel></rss>